Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.; 3 electronic discs (cd-rom)
  - Mr. Black and Carlos (Part 2), dale10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Mr. Black and Carlos (Parts 3 -6), Vic Collins, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Mr. Black and Danny, Dale10, 1999, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Mr. Black and the FBI (Parts 3,4,7,9,10,11,18), Dale10, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Mr. Black Hits the Mark, Maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Mr. Black in Las Vegas, Maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mr. Black's Family Fun, Dale10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mr. Black's Interview, Dale10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Mr. Black's New Year Bash, Maipenraikhap, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Mr. Black's Return, Vic Collins, Undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Mr. Black's Visit, maipenraikhap, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Muscles and Sweat (Parts 1-3), Vincent Hadley, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - My Army Dad, Man45years, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - My Awakening (Parts 3,4), Rim4you, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - My Best Friend's Dad, Story Teller, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - My Best Friend's Father (Parts 1-3), fernandobuddy2002 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - My Big Brother (Part 1), Maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - My Black Construction Dad (Parts 1-3), Fleetwood, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - My Black Neighbors II, Mike (Filemup), 2001; My Next Visit, Mike (Fillemup) (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - My Blind Date, Rocky, Undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - My Boyfriend, Maipenraikhap, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - My Boyfriend: After School, Dale10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - My Boyfriend: All In the Family & In the Morning, Dale10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - My Candyass Kinky Boys, JayKingHoff, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - My Dad, the Marine II (Parts 3-5), Rimpigfl, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - My Dads a Horny Bastard (Parts 2-3), JasonsFury, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - My Desert Storm Trooper, Question Mark, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - My Dream II, Jon Hold, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - My First Marine (Parts 1-3), Rimpigfl, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - My First Time With a Hairy Daddy, Not My Last, Daddy's Boy, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - My Friend Steve, Slick, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - My Gardener, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - My Kinky Fantasy Brought to Life, Ezgoing, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - My Life As A Whore (Part 9,10,15-18), Joe Webster, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - My Master, My Son (Parts 3-7, 10), Dennis, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - My Military Carrer, Dick Hunter, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - My Military Carreer: Parts 8 - 10, Gaybottom, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - My Nasty Dad (Parts 1-3), Rim4you, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - My New Life (Part 21- 24), Joe Webster, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - My Setter, CoachinDC, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - My Shame (Part 9), Maipenraikhap, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - My Son's First Cum, Pedman, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - My Step-dad and Me, Dr. Good, Undated (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - My Thoughts On Last Night, Unknown; Hand, Unknown; Campground Piss Fest, Unknown; The Sewer Plumbers, Unknown, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - N.Y.P.D Slut, Outlaw, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - The Nate Hunter Saga - Chapter 1: Jail Bikers, Jack Forester and Eric, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Navy Relief, Awrt96, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - The Neighbor Owns Me, Imyours497, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Neighborhood Slut, Joe Law, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Net Connect (Hot Jock), Fred, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Netting a Fisherman, Willi Edwards, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - The New Guy Upstairs, Palucca69, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - New Piggy, Devil Di Angelo, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - New Piggy, Use_me27, Undated (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - New Story for a Cop Botherer, copsucker 99, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Next Door Dog (Part 6), Pseudonym Station, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Nick's Big Pexs 4 (Chapters 1-7), Acepecs, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Night at the Brothel, joey1for, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Night At The Brothel, Luvtop, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Night Call, Bill Drake, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Night In the Woods, Creature, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - A Night on the Road, Jake C, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Northern Woods Retreat III, WIWIWI, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Not Exactly, yourpighole, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Obsessed, Obsessed 4, Undated (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Obtuse Triangle, R. Keith Peck, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Odessa Ranch (Parts 1-3), Savagetrainer, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - The Officer and the Quarterback, Bill Drake, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Officer Cole's Secret, glaucon55, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Officer's Boytoy, Unknown, Undated (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Oh Daddy My Daddy (Parts 3,5,6,7,8,10,11), K (I am K), 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Oh Yeah, Unknown, Undated (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Oil Rig, Richard Clark, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - On the Range (Parts 1,5,7,8,11,12), Joe Law, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - One Sunday Evening/Night, Sxuldev8, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - One Wednesday Afternoon, Sxuldev8, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Open Up, Unknown, Undated (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Oral Rape: My Fantasy, Mickey (Daddy), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Orgy Boy, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Our Italian Storekeeper 3, Fleetwood, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Out of Control (Part 2), Dogslife, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Paid in the Pitt, larry76712, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - The Paperboy, Dale10, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Parents Weekend (Chapters 1,5-8,10), billdrake, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Park Knights, JDL896, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Park Ranger, Michael D. Yoder, Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Party at Pops? (Part 2,3,5,6), Unknown, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Paul's Posession, F150satx, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Peeking Into the Garage, Bawdy Pen, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Peeping Toms (Parts 1-3), Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Perils of Greggie-Poo: Episode 7, The Poem, ScatWoman, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Phone Repair, Douglascr, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Pickle Park Dilema, Truckhawk AKA Desertbear, Undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Pico, M, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - The Pig: At the Lakefront Festival, Dale10, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Pig for Cock, Devil Dog, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Pig Pit Stop, Tommy Bear, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Pig Slut (Chapter 1), Btmscott, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The Pig: Visit to a Bookstore, Maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Piglet, Blackflag, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Piss Fag, Unknown, Undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Piss Freak, Ron Kelly, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Piss Party in the Tearoom, JDL896, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Piss Slave, An70874, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Pissy, Cagecashier, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Pit Stop, Nathan Harvey, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Play Pen Eight, Bob Archman, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Playing In the Shed, Black Flag, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Playing With Dad 1, Phil, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Please, Dad!, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Pleasing My Daddy (Parts 1-6), Terry, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - The Plumbers, CobbleHillGuy, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - A Plumber's Tale, Dirt Pig, Undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Poker Buddies, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Police Bitch, Nathan Harvey, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - The Prime Mission (Chapters 1, 2-7, 9), Falcon30, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Prison Food (Parts 1- 3), Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Prison Scat (Parts 1-4), Kyle Porter, Undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Private Lessons (Parts 1-3), Rim4You, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - To Protect and Serve, Desert Rat, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Pumpin Cops, Cooper, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Punks, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Put In My Place, SlaveBoy232, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Putrid Liquid, Micfriend, Undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Queering Sgt. Strait (Parts 1,3-5), Cooper Smith, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Racial Issues, Roderick Shafton, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Ranch Hand - From the Oracle BBS, Unknown, Undated (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Ranch Workout, Silicondog, Undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Raunch, Rick Wagner, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Raunch Night, Gayskin, Undated (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Raunchy Boy (Parts 1-6), Rim4You, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Raunchy Studs (Parts 1- 3), Rim4You, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Raunchy With Dad, Marc, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Real Chat Text - Man and 18 Year Old, l@flash.net, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Really Hairy Family (Parts 1,2), Story Teller, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - The Recycling, Twenty Bucks, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Redneck Fucked by Giant Black Cock, Lives to Tell Tale, R. Keith Peck, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - RepoMan, An668681, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Revenge on Private Ryan, Alex J, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Rick and the Bike Gang, Greg Cherry, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Ricky and Vito, Dirt Pig, Undated (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Roadside Attraction (Parts 1,2), Scatboy001, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Roadside Raunch, Steve Kafe, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Roadwork, Unknown, Undated (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Rocky's Summer Camp, Butc0, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Rocky's Summer Camp, Butch; College Crap, Pigboy; Eating Brian, Sewer Rat, Undated (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Rod of Might, R. Keith Peck, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Roofers, Scott Brenson, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - The Rookie, Bawdy Pen, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Rookie Bar Slut, Kyle_14, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - The Room, maipenraikhap, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Rough Handsome Mexican, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Roughneck Lust, Da Cooper, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Roughneck Lust, Furr, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Roving Reporter (Parts 4,6), Bawdy Pen, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Sailors Do It Deeper, Slick, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Sam's Story, Unknown, Undated (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Sarge, Ralph, Undated (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Sarge, Butch His Dad and I (Parts 1-3), Nick, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Saturday Morning Raunch, Joewilson583, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Say Uncle, Vashon Logwood, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Scenes With Watersports, Slick, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Scent Pig (Parts 1-3), Eric_Jerry, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Sears Stalls,1998 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Service Station, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Service Whore, Scedmark, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Sewer Rats, Mike Kliewer, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Sex and the Signal Guy, cgard43, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Sex Raunch, Bawdy Pen, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Sexual Assault (Parts 2,3), Phill, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Shane, Yard Man, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Shane's Football Injury, Jim Allen, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Sharing Memories, Jason Taylor, Undated (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Sheriff Parker (Part 49), Sky King, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Sheriff Parker (Part 52), Hulcap, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Sheriff Parker Cock Expert (Parts 1-5), Unknown, Undated (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Shipping Dock Raunch, Joe Wilson, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Shit Fuck, Marc, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Shit Games, Unknown, Undated (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Shit Mail (Numbers 1-6), Butch, Undated (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Shit Sex 101, slick, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Shit Slave, Arablover, Undated (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Shitty Attraction; Mr. Ass' Story Room, Mr. Ass, Undated (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Show Off, BigRedOne, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Sir Let Me Drink His Piss, Anartist, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Skid Marks, Scatboy001, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - The Skinhead and His Spider, Outbacker, Undated (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Slave Boy's Punishment From Master, Biker, Undated (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Slave to Cock, An204073, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Slave Wedding, Malestory, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Sleazy Stud (Part 3), Marc, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - Slugger and the Batboy, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Slut Beginnings (Part 1), Matthew Taylor, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Slut Boy (1, Too & More), Billy Boy, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Sneaky Intruder, Roderick Shafton, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - Snotty Kid, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - Soldier's Boy: The Moaning After (Part 2), Plow Boy OH, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - Soldier's Boy: Pryed and Prejudice - Part 5, Andrew Renz, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - Solo Sperm Feast in the Making, Rob, Undated (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - Some Public Sex, Michael, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - Southern Mechanic, PghDude, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Special Gloryhole, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 121)
  - Splatter 1.1, Unknown, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 122)
  - The Stables, Nathan Harvey, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 123)
  - The Stall, Doug192, Undated (Box 25, Folder 124)
  - The Stallion Rides, R. Keith Peck, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 125)
  - Staying with Aunt Evelyn (Parts 1-3,5,7), Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 126)
  - Stephen's Cock Control, Glaucon55, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Still a Bitch, Tom Story, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Story, Spanamer, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Story of Scott (Part 2), Strokedude29, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Straight (?) Brother, Balsam8, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Straight Buddy Ray; Straight Buddy Ray's Lil Bro Joey; and Straight Buddy Ray: Lil Joey Goes Greek; Jon Royale, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Straight Buddy Ray's Teen-age Confidential, Jon Royale, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Straight Learning Curve, Aussie Slick, Undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Strange Days At The Clinic, Loopy, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Strictly Business, Parisboi, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Stroke-n-Sniff, Rim4you, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Stuck on the Rock, Devil Dog, 2000; Agua Para El Papi Cholo, Tommyhawk1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Stud Cop on Campus (Chapter 5), PhinnyGene, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Subway Encounter, Dick Hunter, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Subway Toilet, Unknown, Undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Suck Job, Unknown, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - A Sudden Urge, Martel, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Swabby's Story, Studebaker62, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Swabby's Tale, Unknown, Undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Sweat, Warren Williams, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Sweaty Septette, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Sweet Revenge, Bawdy Pen, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Swordfish (Sleepover), Darner987; (Kein Thema) Darner987; My Mouth Full, Manx952joy; Faggot- Cont., Manx952joy; His Sweaty Legs Pressed Up Against Mine, Manx952joy; The Club, Darner987, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The TACS Club, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Take Me to the Limit, S. Brenson, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Taken For A Ride, Jaime Anderson, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Taking A Piss, Slick, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Taking First Piss, Jon Himus, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - The Taste of Sweat, Don Azars, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - A Taste of Their Own Medicine, nec125, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Teaching Coach the Lesson (Part 1), Douglas McLeod, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Team Reward (Parts 1-7), Bill Drake, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - The Team's Morale Booster, Mike Kliewer, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - A Teenage Summer, Clark Smith, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Teens in Jocks, Warren Williams, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - The Telephone Conversation, Roderick Shafton, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Temptations Path (Parts 1,2), Joe Law, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Terrence Takes on His Teacher, TunsofFun, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Terry's Lessons (Chapter 10-11,13), Shaver Boy, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - That Musk Ain't Aftershave, Roderick Shafton, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Theater Whore (Parts 1,2), Tom Straw, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Theo the Janitor, Unknown; Dirt Pig at the Brown Bungalows, Dirt Pig, Undated (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Three Studs and a Willing Hole (Parts 2,3), Splits, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Through Man a Mighty River Flows, R. Keith Peck, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Thy Neighbors Wife and Husband, Joseph_S1, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Tim and Buddy, Shitbreath, Undated (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Timothy, Colt, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Titus the Cop 2, Twenty Bucks, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Toilet Paper, Chaoshead, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Toilet Sex With Dad, Rim4You, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Toilet Sex With Dad, Rim4You, 2000; Nasty Chat Buds (Part 2), Dude X, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Toilet Trash Turnaround, Lance Rush, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Training Continues, Isuckall, Undated (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Trash Man (Part 1), Unknown, Undated (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Trreat the Trick, Rim4You, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - A Trio of Truckers, cgard43, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Truck Rape Cop (Part 3), Copsucker_99, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Truck Stop, Joe Wilson, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Truck Stop Adventures (Parts 1-2), Joe Law, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Trucker Adventures (Part 2), Joe Law, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - The Trucker and The Biker, Steve in Hotlanta, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - The Trucker and the Hitchhiker Get to it, Gettooit, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Trucker Reunion 2001, GregBear, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Truckers Dream, Truckers Nightmare, Grizzy Scribe, Undated (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Truckers House, Anonymous, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Truckers Load (Parts 1,2,6,7), Mike Kliewer, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Trucker's Boy Toy, I.K., 2000 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Trucker's Gloryhole: Getting It From the Big Boys, Joey, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Truckhawk, GregBear, Undated (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Trucking With Dad and Uncle Steve, Balsam8, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Truckstop Latrine, Balls187, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Truckstop Rape (Part 1), Redragon, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - True Confessions of an Oklahoma Toilet Boy: A Trilogy of Turds, RimmerBoy (ScatDude); One Wednesday Afternoon, Sxuldev8, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - The Two Fullbacks, JamesTBell, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Two Men from the Barracks, Lance Kester, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Two New Toys, William A. Lepeak, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Uncle Bruno's Bedroom, Ethan Coleman, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Uncle Chris's Party, Joe Law, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Uncle Donovan (Parts 5-7, 9-11), Casey Jordan, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Uncle Jack Takes Charge, Journey, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Uncle Jack Two Uncle Jake- Part 2, Bob Archman, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Uncle Joe, Michael D. Yoder, Undated (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Uncle John - A Series, Matt Diermier, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Uncle Leon's Anger, Bawdy Pen, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Uncle Louie (Part 1), twofoldman, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Uncle Red's Garage, GregBear, Undated (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Uncles Slutboy (Parts 1,2,5,10,11,13,16,17,18), Joe Law, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Under Construction, Scott Brenson, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Under the Goal Posts, Eric Madsen, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Untitled (GDShiteater Stories) (Parts 1-4), K.R., Undated (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Untitled, Kenny B, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Untitled, Larry Johnson, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Untitled, Spanamer, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Untitled, Unknown, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - Untitled, Unknown, Undated (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - UPS Fun, Unknown, Undated (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Used By Jock 3, Warren Greene, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Verbal Abuse From the Agency Jock, Kuhdupu, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Video (Part 2), Lilglex666, Undated (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Video Booth (Part 1), LilAlex666, Undated (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Video Booth Head (Chapters 1,2), Noone and PupDoesIt, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - A Vignette, Dale1, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - The Vikes With the Bike, David L. Hass, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - Vivid Imagination, Anthony, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - Wanting More Raunch (Parts 1-3), Steve Kafe, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - The Warehouse 2, Fleetwood, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Watching the Miners (Parts 1- 8), Peter Nixon, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - The Waterboy, Boysub3; Jock Doc, David White; Locker Room, Jerry Gaither, Undated (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - We Three As Told By Jon Hold, Jon Hold, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - Wedding Ball Blueboys, Jon Royale, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 110)
  - The Wedding Gift, Maipenraikhap, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 111)
  - Weekend at the Lake, proflew, Undated (Box 26, Folder 112)
  - Weekend Liberty in San Diego, MaheimEins, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 113)
  - Welcome to the Joint, Cocksucker, Ivan the Gypsy, Undated (Box 26, Folder 114)
  - Wet and Messy (Volumes 1-4), Stephen Holden, Undated (Box 26, Folder 115)
  - Wet Boy, Hal Courtenay, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 116)
  - A Wet Evening, Stephen Brown, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 117)
  - What I Saw (Part 1), Bobysboi, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 118)
  - Where ya headed, Sarge?; Steve Giammarco, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 119)
  - While the Cat's Away (Part 3), Policefan36, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 120)
  - Whoring With Dad (Part 1), Gloryhole_junkie, Undated (Box 26, Folder 121)
  - Wilson's Hollow (Parts 4, 6), Bob Archman, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 122)
  - The Workman, Da Copper, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 123)
  - YMCA (Part 2), Trainman, Undated (Box 26, Folder 124)
  - You Know You Like It, Stevey, Undated (Box 26, Folder 125)
  - CD-R discs titled "Nifty" with saved story files (3 discs), 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 126)
- Series IX. Films, 1981-2007, undated; 6 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons.; 173 videocassettes (vhs); 120 videodiscs (dvd)
  Organized into two subseries:
  Subseries IX.A. Videocassettes (VHS), 1981-2004, undated
  Subseries IX.B. Videodiscs (DVD), 1995-2007, undated
  This series contains gay pornographic films recorded on VHS and DVD.
  - Subseries IX.A. Videocassettes (VHS), 1981-2004, undated; 4 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons.; 173 videocassettes (vhs)
    The VHS tapes are listed alphabetically by title, followed by production company name.
    This subseries consists of gay pornographic films in VHS format, covering a variety of sexual interests and themes.
    - Amazon Adventures, Kristen Bjorn, Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 1996 (Box 27)
    - Animals, Paul Morris, California, Palm Drive Video, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Ass Lick Alley, All Worlds Video, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Barracks Glory Hole #6, 1996 (Box 27)
    - Before & After, California, SX Video, Undated (Box 27)
    - BHV - 9 Hog's Banquet, Undated (Box 27)
    - BHV 7 - Very Yellow with Stains of Brown, Undated (Box 27)
    - Basic Training S.F + Horseman 2000, Undated (Box 27)
    - The Best of Frank Vickers, Christoper Rage, 1991 (Box 27)
    - Bic: Cop Interludes, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated (Box 27)
    - Bic: Cops & Throbbers, California, Palm Drive Video, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Bic: Sex Ptrol, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated (Box 27)
    - Big Bruno, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated (Box 27)
    - Big Guns, California, Laguna Pacific Ltd Video, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Billy Herrington's Body Shop, California, All Worlds Video, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Blue Collar White Socks, T&T Productions, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Blue Collar: White Heat, California, Vivid Video, Undated (Box 27)
    - Bulge, Undated (Box 27)